
NAME
    Install-Crypto
    
SYNOPSIS
    Crypto-Detect will install FSRM on a local or remote server when specified. You can also Detect Mapped drives that have been configured by Group Policies on the domain. 
    There is an option to test the FSRM configuration on the local or remote server.
    
    The folders do not need to be mapped for this to work. Any Shared folder will work with Crypto-Detect.
    
SYNTAX
    Install-Crypto [<CommonParameters>]
    
    
DESCRIPTION
    [1] Install FSRM on Local server
        Istalls FSRM on the local server and imports the FileGroup definitions and a screen template.
        Checks to see if FSRM is already installed and if not it will be installed first.
        You will be prompted to add an email SMPT server, admin email address that will be used to recieve the alerts and a From address also.
        Next you will be prompted to add the Mapped drive folder paths for each share you wish to protect.
    
    [2] Detect all Mapped drives on Domain
        This will run the Get-GPPDriveMaps.ps1 script which will be in the same directry at the DetectCrypto script.
        This will prompt for a Domain Controller in the current domain and search and list all drives which have been mapped via GPO.
     
    [3] Install FSRM on Remote server
        This allows you to Install FSRM and imports the FileGroup definitions and a screen template on a remote server in the domain once specified.
        Checks to see if FSRM is already installed and if not it will be installed first.
        You will be prompted to add an email SMPT server, admin email address that will be used to recieve the alerts and a From address also.
        Next you will be prompted to add the Mapped drive folder paths for each share you wish to protect.
    
    [4] Set Email Config on FSRM
        Alloows you to change the email configuration settings for SMTP server, defualt receipt address and the From address for a local or Remote server.
        
    
    [5] Protect File share on Local server
        Allows you to update the lcoal FSRM server with new File Screens to protect Shared/Mapped drive folder paths.
    
    [6] Protect File Share on Remote server
        Allows you to update a Remmote FSRM server with new File Screens to protect Shared/Mapped drive folder paths.
    
    [7] Test Crypto Detect
        Tests the setup of the FSRM server, which will send an email after protecting a dummy folder c:\Test_Share and adding a +recover+ file.
     
    [8] Update Crypto Definitions
        Allows you to update the crypto definitions on a local or remote server.  This is useful when an Ransomeware Crypto-Detect has not seen before, which can
        be added to the FSRM server detection proccess.  You would have to do this on each server.
    

PARAMETERS
    <CommonParameters>
        This cmdlet supports the common parameters: Verbose, Debug,
        ErrorAction, ErrorVariable, WarningAction, WarningVariable,
        OutBuffer, PipelineVariable, and OutVariable. For more information, see 
        about_CommonParameters (http://go.microsoft.com/fwlink/?LinkID=113216). 
    
INPUTS
    
OUTPUTS
    
    -------------------------- EXAMPLE 1 --------------------------
    
    C:\PS>Example of how to use this cmdlet
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    -------------------------- EXAMPLE 2 --------------------------
    
    C:\PS>Another example of how to use this cmdlet
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
RELATED LINKS
    https://community.spiceworks.com/how_to/100368-cryptolocker-canary-detect-it-early
    http://jpelectron.com/sample/Info%20and%20Documents/Stop%20crypto%20badware%20before%20it%20ruins%20your%20day/1-PreventCrypto-Readme.htm



